<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quill.Codes</title>
    <link>https://quill.codes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Quill.Codes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:22:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://quill.codes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Prototyping: Build a Url Shortener with .NET</title>
      <link>https://quill.codes/posts/fast-prototyping-url-shortener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 09:22:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quill.codes/posts/fast-prototyping-url-shortener/</guid>
      <description>Fast Prototyping and Learning to Code Take a moment to think of your preferred way to learn a new language, framework, or skill. Most likely, there is a certain amount of value that you only get when learning by doing.
I had an interesting transition into development. I already knew a bit about how to code, but I had never had a programming job. At the time, I was working for a company where the dev department was willing to give me a chance, so they sent me an assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Class Fields Using &#39;out&#39; Parameters</title>
      <link>https://quill.codes/tips/set-class-fields-with-out-parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 12:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quill.codes/tips/set-class-fields-with-out-parameters/</guid>
      <description>Did You Know? You can set class fields with &amp;lsquo;out&amp;rsquo; method parameters Whether you like out parameters or not in C#, they are here to stay. They decorate a number of common patterns in the .NET ecosystem.
 The TryParse pattern where the return is a bool that indicates success and your parse result comes from the out parameter.  However, very often you want to set your class field with the parse result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dont Fear the // Todo</title>
      <link>https://quill.codes/tips/dont-fear-the-todo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:58:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quill.codes/tips/dont-fear-the-todo/</guid>
      <description>Did You Know? Visual Studio tracks your &amp;ldquo;// TODO&amp;rdquo; comments so you can find them later. From within Visual Studio Go to View -&amp;gt; Task List. This will display the Task List window and show you any area of your open Solution. You can even filter down to your Current Project, Current Document, or Open Documents.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t just recognize // TODO, but will also recognize // HACK What if I Don&amp;rsquo;t Use English?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Objects: A Beginning Approach to Object Oriented Design</title>
      <link>https://quill.codes/posts/practical-objects-a-beginning-approach-to-object-oriented-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quill.codes/posts/practical-objects-a-beginning-approach-to-object-oriented-design/</guid>
      <description>The Goal of Practical Objects I love programming, but programming is hard and existing paradigms that inflexibly insist upon perfection do not make it easier. This is not to say that paradigms and patterns produce bad code, but certain statements from peers, thought leaders, and friends permeate the space in my head when attempting to solve problems.
 &amp;ldquo;This approach is better because it runs faster&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;This code violates SOLID&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We should roll our own library instead of using this framework&amp;rdquo;  I took these statements to heart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>